(Penny:)Your friend's really cute.
Anything going on with you two?
Leslie?
No, no. What, are you kidding?
(Sheldon:)He asked her out once.
It was an embarrassing failure.
(Leonard:)Thank you, Sheldon.
(Leonard:)I'm sorry.
Was that supposed to be a secret?
(Penny:)That's too bad.
You guys would make a cute couple.
- Oh, dear.
- What's the matter?
(Raj:)She didn't take my order.
How could she take your order
when you're too neurotic to talk to her?
(Raj:)Nevertheless,
this will be reflected in her tip.
LEONARD: What did Penny mean,
"you'd make a cute couple"?
(Sheldon:)I assume she meant
the two of you...
(Sheldon:)...would constitute a couple
that others might consider cute.
An alternate and less likely interpretation
is that you could manufacture one.
As in, "Look, Leonard and Leslie
made Mr. and Mrs. Goldfarb.
Aren't they adorable?"
(Leonard:)If Penny didn't know
that Leslie had turned me down...
...then that would mean that she, Penny,
thought I should ask her, Leslie, out...
...indicating that Penny had no interest
in me asking her out.
(Leonard:)But because she did know
I had asked Leslie out...
...and that she, Leslie,
had turned me down...
(Leonard:)...then she, Penny,
could be offering consolation.
"That's too bad,
you would have made a cute couple."
(Leonard:)But while thinking,
"Good, Leonard remains available."
(Sheldon:)You're a lucky man, Leonard.
(Leonard:)How so?
(Sheldon:)You're talking to one of
the three men in the West...
(Sheldon:)...capable of following
that train of thought.
Well, what do you think?
(Sheldon:)I said I could follow it,
I didn't say I cared.